# FALGUN BHATT



Address F-501, Vandematram Prime, Opp Swaminarayan temple, Gota, Ahmedabad. Gujarat, India

#### Email:

bhatt7falgun@gmail.com

**Mobile No.:** 8511320852

Date Of Birth: 07 March 1994

Gender: Male

**Nationality**: Indian

Marital Status: Unmarried

### Language Known:

English, Hindi, Gujarati, Sanskrit

#### **Interested Area:**

Internet Surfing, Management and all types of computer work, Acting, Story making, sport games.

### Summary

I have 4 years' experience in IT industry. I have knowledge about Data Analysis I just Complete my Data Science course. I have experience in web research, Data Mining, Data Management, and so on. Where the work environment is congenial to utilize my full potential and prove my utmost commitment. Where I can learn and enrich myself for better service.

### Skill Highlight

- Data Science
- Data Mining
- Data Management
- AI/ML Algorithms

- Python Programming
- Deep Learning, Big Data
- Team Management
- Web Research

### Experience

## Hidden Brains InfoTech Pvt. Ltd. - 2021 – Present Data Analyst

- Analysis of Recruitment Data. Manage data and Mine the data about profiles.
- Manage Google Sheets, Report Generate using Recruitment software.
- Generate offer proposals; manage the joiner details and all.

## **K2 Data Search** – 2020 to 2021 **Web Researcher, Data Researcher**

Web research over client requirement, Lead the team, and trained new joiners.

## Hindus Software – 2019 to 2020 Junior Developer

 Here I can learn about .Net, PHP, android program development techniques. Also I can develop some website in HTML, CSS, and WordPress.

### **UniquesData** – 2012 to 2015

#### **Team Leader**

• Here I was start with data entry operator and after some time I was promoted to Team leader.

### Education

Bachelor of Computer Application – 2020 to 2022 at **Dr. BAOU**, Ahmedabad Diploma in Computer Engineering – 2016 to 2019 at **G.T.U**, Ahmedabad

### Certification

Digital Marketing Course (Google)
Complete Data Science Course (Udemy)